is there ever the possibility of fooling
the endocrine system into maintaining
your endogeneous test production whilst
adding exogenous test or is this just
simply
impossible well I don't know why you'd
want to honestly um because you're
you're competing cross purposes there
because PE there are clinics that try to
push this right they'll say here's your
encline that you're going to take
alongside your testosterone or here's
your uh ratas inhibitor so if they keep
the estrad low then maybe we're going to
trick the system into pumping out a
little more natural you're you're still
fighting yourself because you're now
blocking you're poisoning you're taking
a poison essentially with those that's
going to cause negative issues while
you're trying to counteract them with
the testosterone it's like you just take
the testosterone if it's a if you want
to keep your natural production going
for fertility reasons and stuff it's a
whole another conversation you know
we've talked about the HCG and FSH
protocols before there's ways to
maintain fertility while you're taking
exogenous testosterone um I would not
personally be taking something that's
inhibiting estrogen or estrogen activity
in the brain just to stimulate my
testical while I'm taking testosterone I
think you're asking to feel like crap
personally